During.
During. During during.
During. During
Duryodhana.
The. Game.
Would have on each prestigious sun the
camel trainers arriving at our base camp.
Days with it was all just
a patient beasts which seemed to sense the
dangerous journey before. At this time
they express my appreciation to the
one man with patience sympathy and
understanding want anyone else made our
expedition possible ladies and gentlemen Dr
Norman Wilkes the president
of Southern Europe US.
Cameleers like most
patient souls more than
a little stubble in the packing developed
in wooden Durance contest between the
beasts and the again it's
too bad this young man was
a few years old and I'm sure you could
have solved the entire problem.
If you love these people ladies and gentlemen
bear in mind in one time in history
again just come they rule the
world and that reminds me of
another unsung hero
a man whose industry negotiated were
responsible for the photographic records of
R.J.
Jelly Frasier cameramen. But
it lacked even the camels are
subdued we started on our trick
a joint in the trunk of the tomb of an
emperor ranger like one of the last great
secrets
followed days of monotonous same this
retarded onward into the desert rock
along Leigh by occasional bits of plate
basically prolong our delivering mail
needed supplies and bringing back our
sick and injured we have the signal of
a talent when we want it you
must realize this is more than
a travelogue we have all the elements of
jump from Mr Rugg obstacles to overcome
even
a suggestion of romance which explains the
frequent trips about oh my God At least
with the caravan and done the deal was
piloting the plane. I checked it was a hit
a do underscore the country across the mount
as we started to climb the temperature
drop precipitously until we were in the
snow country as you can see by the way the
camels are found this is not the easiest
part of object but at last the summit is
reached we began to step toward our
objectives I promise you on an interesting
surprise here it is the discovery of the
Empress to which whereabouts at the main
the mystery or such shock of
discovery was too much for
a sudden realisation after the hardships
of our journey would gradually the
enormity of our find it was just us we
called which are in our excitement and
rushed into the to have lived right.
Here it is rebounded the jungle. My
camera and I recall reading that.
Last time the grand.
Pope's condition
a lot of us are divided I guess yet the
toughest in their lives that my friendship
. My particular cup existed in my
hair in here and I try holy fuck.
The Johnnies there as it was
a custom I can say to that I only know that
our troubles began from that moment of
I will stop said the punished
frightening our care
we are worked hard combat
the elements why but
a success of our expedition based on
our copilot seemed very much when. We
started out to revisit the to what the GOT
LOST THE try to stop when morning if not
bitter wind increased and violence. Such
a body. Without Mason I would like to take
this opportunity to pay tribute to Mason
this gallant member of our party who did
so much to help achieve our success my
Chinese parents became very strict
a strong US I was faced with
a hard decision weight and
endanger the lives of our party.
I decided on the medical.
Examiner When I began the difficult task
of translating the scope that I really
found out the magnitude
of our discovery. Where I
studied its contents more I
realized that I.
Really. Like.
Whatever space I don't like.
What's wrong or
a title no Something happened. Here
he was there was
a lecture Jimmy Bartel be disappointed my
only excuse is that I misunderstood the
time perhaps we can learn the pictures
again I hope so anyway as one of Dad's
favorite I never could get my
chance to knock the ology given by
a plane and after all there are many reasons
for wanting to go on an archaeological
trip to China is
a complete camera report I raise to start
the film and are you listening to me yes
yes thank you. I wish they'd
have just been out there
a long time now don't worry it has been
under strain the work and study preparing
for the lectures been too
much for missionaries Yes
children the I want the
best is crush Steve.
Moore. Leads police.
Police this way to see if
nobody leaves or Grady.
What's all the excitement about I don't
know but I must be serious I was captain
straight of the Homicide Squad homicide yes
that means the talk that I'm afraid so
.
You can keep murder out of the newspapers
we have no proof that you made your own
doctor said he was poisoned you
tell me were stricken down
a lecture does look like suicide and
then. What I want to know is who had the
brilliant idea of moving
your body I did it wasn't
a body just my very dear friend Dr Ben
we are supposed to get collapse from
overwork and have been and human to left
him on the floor Yeah but it might help me
a little I suppose
a photograph or body at the scene of the
crime I got work to do prints clues
routine to go through perhaps this was
a routine crime to you my name is wrong
James Lee Why are you fit into this
Dr Benton had just returned from the interior
of China and Chinese the Chinese tell
us that two of you work together and if
you are like our go yourself for me so.
You know what
a Dr Ben have for lunch dare devil to
feel him in it on the desert again that
before you get it that's for everybody
else had the same thing everybody here
except Miss when men but she had chaps
only know so she had a cup of coffee and
a piece of apple pie. He's had the same
lunch every day from me she to Rolla time
she lives here when Len is it I should
say was Dr Ben secretary All right all
right I want to read
you though I was there
a plane pilot on the expedition and I
was the camera man I ran the projection
machine at the lecture What's
your active research losses with
him at the lecture doctors not only met
up stair the trustee the university and
a few friends I was with the money died
Jonas and I did he say anything research as
a matter of fact he did it because I
didn't mention it before because it didn't
make sense come on what do you say well
there we could hardly hear and it was
something about eternal fire and that when
Elaine will what do you know about this
plane arriving at our I have no idea what
the Dr met when Dr Benton phoned me he
hinted at something important
he had found there was
a Skrull did you have them translated
now doctor that when that anyone wait
a minute wait
a minute scrawl eternal fire translate what
is our life well the doctor was telling
us about finding an ancient scroll in the
Tomb of the Ming Emperor where it is now
in the state who has the combination Dr
Ben and Dr Weil of course being President
of the college I have the combinations of
every second the campus Come on come on
assault on the right.
By there's nothing in there the skull guard
Yes I was my patients Now listen I'm
sick of scrolls translations eternal
fire I'm going to have just
a slight dash on murder mystery shift
and he said Corey I'm
aside and all this great
speech I want you to send some men up to
Rule number four electoral number for the
Southern University that's right Doug
Bentley Yep you know Prince photographs the
works yeah.
Chinese exchange. Chinese
exchange well last time burned
down.
Yes.
I was just to show the Chinese me wants
to get you know Jim Jonas must have been
scared that I was full
of cats and he takes
a chance on finding out what I want to go
by Jonas doesn't turn out to be our job
certain able to give
a lot to know that you didn't die
in that Chinese desert well. I
never enjoyed working for you figured out.
Graving full late again I may not
like your way delay. Thanks but I
question the breakfast Thanks
a lot you know lunch how you expect fine
Carola you know can't find home how you
know I love college in each other you
go dark abandoned the bend and die. But
nice going maybe I ought to let you hunt
killer while I stay home and cook you
coke.
My name not the way you name food Well
it may be people in China but in America
it's all you. How dark abandoned
kill poison what kind poison
nobody knows until the police surgeon
performs in our party Sure maybe Dr Bandon
had
a bad clerk. Questionnaire
you play games you know there's something
wrong with these pictures and now the
wrong words look you know really.
That said I've got you've got
what I've got what's wrong with the picture
is the want to pitch look see this
picture that the Benton as he started the
election see the rabbit join the table
see this picture of the lecture room after
Dr Bentley collapsed where the water
pitcher was not this one we haven't time
to cry you know you'll find out about him
why don't I think of that
before. Everybody plays the.
Thousand fingerprints twenty five suspects
Chinese temples I'm missing stroke and
a title fire I want to chase. Hell out
yeah. Yeah OK thanks and not some kind
of an awful lot of poison nobody knows
anything about.
A great economy what do you
think that is maybe it's the
you can also find.
An answer to find any other place the next
he said heard. I would say is I'd like
a red lantern on one snap out of
it or whatever I was searching
something could be it's even had you
know what we're looking for this
I don't know how you're mixed up in all of
this but maybe I've got some you figured
the poison was in the drinking water all
the time right right and in the excitement
following Dr Fenton school at the murder
through the water pitcher and glass out
the window of the window was open during
the lecture how do you know I opened
a doctor that not me killed when I hit
you on the head was probably looking for
pieces of this yes he probably found the
picture being heavier didn't break Luckily
I held that piece of the glass in my hand
luckily for you were didn't cut your hand
off. You sure you didn't hear see anyone
not exactly I did see what appeared to be
a flashlight in the shrubbery Now it's
your turn I too saw lightning shrubby
hurried over and found Mr Wong lying on
the ground I was doing my best to revive
him when you arrived sure you didn't
hit him on the head in the first place
positive but I did hear someone running
away. A mysterious character shrouded in
darkness what are you don't smoke in around
the grounds I wasn't snooping I was on
my way here you asked me to come over here
you know it's right I did in there again
a flashlight where no no of course matters
to simply sample how do we even know
there's a glass doc then
drag out we don't but
a simple laboratory I know all about that
all right you two run along thank you
Captain and make ready to go down the
lavatory and have it tested for
a place where would you be check with
you later at the station treated as.
Going to take you somewhere
you know thanks I'm to
a doctor then that's good you'll have no
trouble reaching there however if you're
not going to talk to Benton's be
careful you're going to be followed
Are you sure I'm going to be solid we're
going to be followed is that better much.
Feel like talking of course but shall
we talk about scrolls ancient ones from
Chinese temples. What
was on it I don't know
usually these girls are merely
a detail survey of all the campus
possessions Dr Benton handed of something
important to tell you what it was you
know he said the lecture was the time and
place to reveal it then his discovery may
have been the reason for the murder and
the saddest I don't know nearly as
a museum piece the scroll is very valuable
granted but why could it have indicated
the location of some hidden treasure. Mr
Wrong I believe you've been reading too
many detective stories.
Is following all right I've got to get
away but if you help me that depends
I'm not running out but there's something
I must do I can explain you've got to
trust me. Hang
on.
All right where you go girl you know you
left the lecture hall and when when life
happens and you can finally now you cut
out that plan where issues. You must have
disappeared all right wiseguy I got the
number that cabin I'm going to have I
picked up.
I wake. Up in the house at
a strange baby set out in order to have
sex again think that number five you'll
sound five one one and
a chance to go away when Lent I
want to pick up those but on
the Gray Yeah yeah thanks OK
say listen all the phone.
I get this I don't just want to follow
his advice on Grand Avenue I want you to
check I send a good man out there I go
over his place with a fine tooth comb
a are keeping veggie for an hour OK.
Well you were right he found poison in
that blacks correspond to the poison darts
in the stomach sure Mr Penfold probably
an oriental but it's deployed when women
know about that wouldn't you. Or any of the
other members of the expedition they're
all in China. Eager to take
a little ride with you taking me in why
would he have been filling the thing that
you don't know about. Now as
a matter of fact the one little house I
want to avoid because so much will oversee
.
You know I'm pretty much of a downer
Chinese temples internal fires manuscripts
a lot of my line but you're Chinese when
you think about my countrymen press
a lot and everything's in fanciful language
eternal fire or maybe something down to
earth may be seasons when
a lamb and there's always Penhallow I don't
think she poisoned her own father and
there's that Tommy once he's named the
avian or Fraser the cameraman I think you
and I Ben are going to complete less of an
explanation don't you it would help also
a list of the people at the lecture whoever
poisoned the lot it was at the lecture
he couldn't very well take
a chance on that water being tasted by
someone else he or she mean I'm not
forgetting when the lamb live and then it
sneaked up there in the dark during the
lecture and put the poison in the water
possibly though you'd think when Len would
have seen that he was facing away from the
screen it's more likely more likely that
when the lamb thanks the whole thing except
for one thing. Well and all the murder
mysteries I've read and seen the person
they throw all the suspicion on is never
the murder. Maybe this
is one time across up
a formula that's too much to hope for by
the way was the film that they were on
this afternoon Frasier. That cameraman
answered why everybody has one advantage on
us they've heard the lecture and
seen the pictures by don't we take
a look if nothing else happens at least
will be even with the rest of them that's
a good idea I got an hour to spare
Miles was spending at the moment he's
six.
And I'll yes begin where. The whole
is it luck
a lot. And
live like anybody don't know.
Are you listening. It's not like.
Very. Well here take this. Well
what happened. I got a phone call
asking me to meet when we learned
a green dragon I started
out suspicious turned
around came home no room for listening Was
it will end on the phone I thought it
was
a red right now thanks than if
anyone when you came in lawyers are.
Somebody searching the place they must have
heard it coming and any idea what they
were looking for no there's
nothing worth taking except.
Thanks to you pilot they didn't have time
to do much damage anywhere whereas the
film of the expedition so I have a right
here on his machine I've been working on
a graduate chemistry my projection machine
is Dillard University However I can run
it through this movie olive oil we use
this for cutting stock and start as you
please that's fine if you
don't mind all not at all.
You have to fill yourself if you're
a one man job. Photograph the
interior of the tomb or yet. It is.
Worth the feeling of just abandon finding
those girls. I haven't got that in fact I
get the one thing about the scroll until
today at the lecture we were all kind of
excited and when Dr Bethany yelled at the
advance the car gets quiet I love the
camera and ran with the others and you
and the others didn't see anything.
So you gave me the deck put in
a phony call that Frazier that broke
into his house that isn't true I never
telephoned then what are you doing here.
Comes to march with your doctor that's why
when I arrived the door
a little thing someone sitting at the
desk as I came in turned around with
a gun in his hand yeah tied you have
a bunch in the closet Why don't you tell
us what happened you were searching the
place raise your crotch in your condom then
tighter self up then put itself in the
closet or Frazier didn't tire up and put
her in the glass and then knock him self
out that you were already
a Frazier. What are you doing here
I thought I heard somebody out so yeah I
know the mysterious stranger again and.
Police Headquarters
on the side and other
streets they can send
a crew of the phrases out front to grab
stranger prints footprints to there may be
a mysterious stranger at
threat that's come on.
They want somebody.
I think you can make.
I got the license number but it's probably
a stolen car yeah we've got to get
out of here before somebody calls
a cop. Well it looks like we got some
minor right where he wants us haven't
accomplished much up what we
sure have done our rights
a little and gave me the slip. You can't
put one over on it and she Yeah looks like
it. That's quite a story
she told want to honor
a moment I don't know but come on up to my
apartment and I'll try to find it's too
late to find out anything
tonight anyway I'll make you
a cup. Of I got fellows. That was OK
yeah but it didn't bother you don't really
know how long I want to go the only
would I not ah they rock What's the matter
fool now much older from day one I don't
want window to hold I had
a minute on the speaking please this is
Captain street scuse the man look the
house I catch you what does he look like
big man big feet where is enough to
show you.
Really.
I hear you said get out.
One of your men Captain
Not as of tomorrow I see good
work now make us some tea for
my captain. That's. A sorry
about having to send a man
a project me but you're going to close.
IT What is your angle on this to
a group of influential Chinese think the
secret of eternal fire is vital to the
defense of China I mean this eternal fire
is really on the level decidedly excuse
me. Janet an exchange please
this is James Lee warm revered
elder please greeting
only the eyebrows of youth would have the
temerity to call the beard of age at such
an hour how great
a blessing is clear perception welcome
James Lee eternal fire is saved not until
Dr Benton's murder is solved
a daughter of the Moon Flower named When
land is concerned she known to the friends
of China
you have added to my already heavy load
of obligation the eyes of the blind. Side
of the temple is in the hands of China's
enemy it is your duty to see that the
secret of eternal fire is not used against
her will happen is an enduring spring
sons to mourn at your grave look I got
trouble without having to worry about
figuring out Chinese proverbs What about
women now Captain just relax we're going
to have
a little tea and then if you'll pick me up
in the morning I think we can get willin
to talk why wait all morning she won't be
going anywhere all right all right bring
on the.
Well it was a caucus from
a Chinese student sir but once complained
about the government number they tell me
that
a Chinese archaeological expedition is
digging up the body of George Washington in
exchange so well it's
a rough idea is when one
hole in the library the
morning of Jimmy tell me I was just leaving
and he knew nothing definite you match
up in St Paul OK you know you did you never
tell meeting. We had one to bother you
most certainly thought of anything that
might help us no no I've racked my brain
gone over and over the whole
expedition How about you Dean this
a copilot Mason for instance can you
tell us anything about him well he was
a peculiar sort of a duck However afraid
he might be able to help you he was
a very good friend of nations Well if
either of you think of anything let us know
where we generally are out early this
morning Never mind that let's get out of
business have you a few
moments of course there are
a few things I like to discuss with you and
I've already told you everything I know
as Dr Benton secretary perhaps but we hope
you talk in your official capacity in
a way to remember me when Len works
for the Chinese government was.
That true yes you'd better tell us all you
know I'm sure your country as well as
mine must want to scroll recovered Naturally
my sympathies follow my heritage but
after all I am an American the secret must
not be used against either country what
is this a spy plot could very
easily be this girl contained
a clue to the temple of
eternal fire there was
a shrine where according to Chinese legend
there than an underlying column of fire
the centuries its location was never known
but one thing was clear from all the
stories coil replenish the flame oil seeping
through the Earth's surface it was no
doubt that if this rain really existed it
must be the largest oil deposit in the
world. Well that's true
that scroll is worth
a fortune that's why my government assigned
me to Dr that and that I failed to see
first too clever for me of course it's
too late to prevent Dr Benson step but
working together we still may retrieve the
skull and save other lives I'll do all
that I can to help you if that's true what
about that hocus pocus of Frazier's last
night I don't know honestly I didn't
telephone him who did face that the call was
in Chinese probably from Chinatown wait
a minute if it was it can be traced to
Chinatown exchange list subscribers by name
after all all we have to do is find the
operator to call Fraser's house it's all
very simple I'll come honest if.
That's not me thank you we have many phone
calls each night but since we know the
approximate time it is possible that one
of the girls will remember Rumsfeld you
were duty last night from eight until
twelve this is Mr Wong Hello Jimmy Jimmy's
brother and I went to high school together
then perhaps we'd better let Mr Y.
Explain with me what Rose This is when Len
and this gentleman is Captain St of the
San Francisco police we are
trying to trace a call to
a Mr Fraser who lives at the old cabin of
peace you know the place yet it is at the
upper left hand corner of my boy rose means
that the phone plugs in there on the
board and she says thank you
good do you remember plugging in
a call for there at approximately eight
o'clock last night we've been in that road
space aboard she might
remember fine. Yes there was
a call from Mr phases where did it come
from I'm sorry I can't locate it exactly
for you the best I can do is be sure it
came from this section all it's fine
Rosalie's you've narrowed it down
Thank you so much you can furnish us
a list of the subscribers whose names are
in this area of course that's of water
for sure that all we've got to do is check
them all and find out which one called
Frazier last night. There are only twelve
named twelve names three of them are
females at the grabbers Suppose we leave
them to win land you and I can track down
the others. This is crazy just
because your friend rose petal has
a brainwave we have to check up on every
Chinese laundry in town and they want to
chance it product maybe you'll feel
better after a little lunch away for just
a child here we are Charlie one.
Welcome play here like Chuck show is now
just looking around charming for Young No
no thanks you here alone us crazy
alone very hard on one man
a wise man understands the seven virtues
of peace why there's one more stone to an
overloaded don't come on there's no harm
in this man. Now your phone sorry no phone
why. No I happen to know there's
a phone in here where is it show it to me
just chap No four nowhere a minute wait
a minute see that it's pretty isn't it
that's me on the lark if you don't tell me
what i Phone is you're going to get it
running abrupt let me talk to me again then
when I ask what it is then maybe you are
legally could and then when I moved
a little wait
a minute what is all as I saw in press
that button and trace the wire to that
closet it looks suspicious. Where's the
phone please no phone Charlie want to
trouble you're going to get in
plenty of trouble come. To the fire.
Service couple.
Look like
a panel how they are naturally
or not one blasted gents. After
you challenge.
That mindset up there those are killers
you see that nice Charlie want.
To. How do you know.
Going someplace Charlie. I was wondering
do you know if you're going to smash or
Jimmy highways I held up come
on you and he's going to have
a little talk come on me going around on
my never mind the jungle I'm going to
sound
a lot like it was. When
you're French I want to file a truck
it was a prisoner not yours until
a little Chinese threat about
the bones of his ancestors sure
a word he didn't want me to
leave arceo to let him wait
a while what did he have to say when the
two men said he didn't know their names
only known as number one and number four
showed him every picture in the place but
he didn't recognize any I'm
told that. You know it's
a funny thing that this knife looks exactly
like the one they threw at you the
other night or doesn't look yet might be
the same night. I beg your pardon
what is that thing
a little trinket you men found when they
searched the hide out in mine laying it
down long enough to listen to me. No of
course not I didn't mean to be rude it's an
interesting piece and I was trying to
trace it I'm sorry it's all right on the
Charlie dropped the bombshell and I want
to wash your face when I spring it on you
I'm all face and ears like claims you didn't
know the two men in the hideout but he
did describe
a frequent visitor who was the jealous
Jonas the Bentley but look that's right
let's get going. Oh good evening good
evening what is Jonas I don't know come
to think of it I haven't seen you for
several hours he's probably
need to read and spend
a lot of time ago in the
house I want to check.
Haven't success is up to you yes that's
why we want Jonas ever see anything like
that before where that said you know they
got adventure I haven't seen since you
were in China where did you get in
a room. How long since you've
seen Jonas he was here.
All right you find him now you know
China so he's scrambling. OK send out
a description on the radio ham picked up
that settles you mean that John is killed
after that but he won't get
far away I can't believe.
Look.
Here on this. The fingerprint or anything
but I still can't understand how they
stuffed them in there without your knowing
about it I'm sorry Captain but my duties
take me all over the house is that I was
working on
a song that's right is until dinner time
and I'm just making nice this case got me
daffy daggers fingerprints scrolls poison.
I lounge have the right
don't say. All right had to say
them OK thanks. Ali I like that
this was stuck in Jonas after eight died
and what killed the same price my killed
back then and I get no place fast
but what do you say master mind
I'm going crazy and you're playing with
a doll I guess we both going crazy
we were talking about this got
a vengeance you called it yes he's
a local deity found among the Nomad cut to
the Gobi Desert in the same district as
the Emperor's tomb yes it's far as I
know that's the only place now wait
a minute children I don't want to hear any
more about Oriental hokus pokus all I
want to know is kill Doc Benton and who
killed you all this I think maybe we're
getting warm any report of the two men
in the motor boat. Harbor Patrol hasn't
turned up a thing I have just
but I might just be looking at
a man it's got five newspapers
a police commissioner in the whole town
around his neck and he asked me am I
desperate I mean desperate enough to try
a long shot Sure I'll
try anything what is.
This
a mild Jimmy long calling. Walling
the startling announcement that Mason the
missing pilot of the Benton expedition
had been found and the
diagnosis of his condition was
a mass of these been taken to St Christopher's
hospital and shortly expected to
regain consciousness the police confidently
expected as soon as he does so they
will obtain valuable information in
the Benson murder investigation.
I run this wherever the want to connect
it up if I'm right the killer will try to
prevent Mason from talking and for tonight
I'm going to be Mason but you may How
can you be sure that Masons are why I can't
but I'm banking on the killer not being
sure either the nation might even be the
killer that's right Jimmy there's nothing
to worry about all we're trying to do
is get these people out in the open
microphone to pick up the slightest noise
ready now to listen and then any trouble
starts we'll notice it was Jimmy Kimmel
slam get to that promise to yell if
anything happens I promise.
A snap out of that is going to happen
to the ground an even kept my eyes.
On the joint right. Sure I've never
seen one of these take God's word yet.
Everything OK. This is station
W all Angie signing off.
That's good keep it.
Thank Grady Come on come on
stay away what time is it. To.
Hide anything.
And then try to keep the same out
of this cup you're going yeah.
You better give me
a couple minutes. The
matter oh I'm sorry
nothing to worry about.
Back to help.
Since then he's been in hiding but I thought
this little trick of yours which more
came out I'm afraid you're going to have
a little trouble getting away I don't think
so three know those aren't we have an
ambulance waiting downstairs a great M.G.
Heard anything on a. Few
minutes ago that was just
a click and then click.
Click Fraiser of long
vision so you could start to get more.
White said something
happens all right I'm in
a stand I want to fix the
thing it was already we've.
Got I got me back. I swear
Jimmy. Well Fraser you better
talk as soon as I saw the film of the
expedition I felt sure that you had cut it
and that the camera had photographed more
than you would. The reason you killed
dark Venice because you didn't want him
to tell about the oil what about he knew
that Fraser had stolen the scroll and was
working with Mason to try to get it back
Fraser killed him you know
a very clever Mr Long but you still haven't
got the scroll and what's more you will
never get it you see I destroyed that
oddly enough I believe you Fraser but you
didn't destroy it without photographing it
scroll itself would have been difficult
to dispose of cites the contents are
the most important thing Captain.
What am I looking for
a film that's
probably it. That's too small
the pictures inside open
May I. This is part of China I think
we can trust you to see that it
remains so what do you think after oh I
think you're right except that I think
someone should go along to help that is
someone who understands the language and
well the customs of
somebody like yourself it's
a wise man who understands and not. Come
on on come
.